exceldatabank.com 2015-12-29

# Untitled Document

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Exceldatabank.com is an online matrimonial portal endeavouring constantly to provide you with premium matrimonial services. Since we are strongly committed to your right to privacy, we have drawn out a privacy statement with regard to the information we collect from you.

**What information you need to give in to use this site?**

The information we gather from members and visitors who apply for the various services of our site includes, email address, first name, last name, a user-specified password, mailing address, zip code and telephone number or fax number.  
If you establish a credit account with us to pay the fees we charge, some additional information, including a billing address, a credit card number and a credit card expiration date and tracking information is collected by our gateway operator "PAYPAL".

**How the site uses the information it collects/tracks?**

Exceldatabank.com collects information from our users primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver Personalized experience.

**With whom the site shares the information it collects/tracks?**

The information collected from any of our users is not shared with any individual or organization.  
Exceldatabank .com does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information at the individual level regarding its customers to any third party. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security. We are also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer.

**Do all visitors have to pay?**  
NO. All visitors to our site may browse the site, search the ads and view any articles or features our site has to offer without entering any personal information or paying money.

**Credit card details of members**

We use Paypal server for credit card transactions to protect the credit card information and your card details are not available to us. 

**How to unsubscribe the membership?**  
The members are requested to login to the relevant pages for unsubscription.

**Can users contact any number of profiles in a single day?**  
As a paid member of this site, you have the privilege to contact hundreds of profiles. However, there is a specified limit to send 100 messages per day due to fair online usage policy.

**Notice**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments or as a result of a change of policy in our company.  
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Statement, please write in to exceldatabank@yahoo.com
